Tomislav Balabanov

Web, UX & UI Designer

tomislay.balabanoy@hotmail.com

Summary

I'm currently studying at Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering in Skopje, Macedonia. Department of application of

E-technologies, Applied E-technologies.

My range of design services includes creating a design for new websites or improving existing ones. I have worked with clients like: Moda Calzini, Beatrix Crew, E-Medical, Timst etc.

I will work with you to discover what you need and create the best solution. My priorities are quality and respect of deadlines and budget. I also loves to share his enthusiasm and passion for design, so feel free to contact.

Experience

Freelance Web Developer at Fiverr

September 2016 - Present

Freelance Web Designer at Freelancer.com

October 2015 - Present

Web Designer at Beatrix Crew

August 2016 - Present

Main part of work consists of Web Designing their website, Managing their Social media and all the IT related needs of the company.

Insurance and finance agent at WVP Group

2015 - Present

my work is consisted of insurance, finance consulting and team work. Which gives a never ending career.

General Manager

July 2016 - August 2016 (1 month)

To monitor the Stuff.

Web Designer

March 2010 - August 2014 (4 years 5 months)

I have a responsibilities for creating the website and menaging social networks.

Founder

October 2008 - January 2010 (1 year 3 months)

I founded HarsoftHC as a hobby first, then it growth to a business. Then i ask a friend to help me so we can accomplish more.

Services that we offered:

- -Formating Computers
- -Web Design
- -Computer Networks
- -Advice for: backing up files, system problems, errors, connection problems.

Education

Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering, Skopje Macedonia

Engineer in Computer Science and Engineering, Department of application of E-technologies, Applied E-Technologies, 2015 - 2018

Saba, Skopje Macedonia

MIddle-school, Computer and Information Sciences, General, 2012 - 2015

Tomislav Balabanov

Web, UX & UI Designer

tomislav.balabanov@hotmail.com



Contact Tomislav on LinkedIn